thisisglamorous.com 2018-06-13

# This Is Glamorous :: Privacy

This Is Glamorous takes privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat and use the information we collect when you visit thisisglamorous.com or sign-up for our newsletter.

## Personal Information

In order to provide you with This Is Glamorous’ newsletter emails, we need your email address. This Is Glamorous does not collect any information except that which is expressly provided by you. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent and will never sell, rent, or share your personal information, including your email to any third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

## Other Information

This Is Glamorous may, from time to time, also request additional information such as age, buying preferences, annual income, or other demographic or profile information. We use this information to better tailor our content and improve the experience on our site. We may also share this information with third parties, such as advertisers, but only in aggregate, anonymous form. No third party will receive information from us that personally identifies you or anyone else in any way.

## Usage Information

In addition to collecting other personal and non-personal information, This Is Glamorous may gather other information on how our site is used. This information is not personally identifiable and will be used to determine how our website is being used. Such information might include: What sites did users come from? How much time they spend on our site? What pages do they view? What sites do they go to? All of this information is collected to help us create a better, faster, more efficient website and provide you with better content.

## How to Opt Out

You can unsubscribe from receiving This Is Glamorous emails at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any email.

## Third-Party Advertising

From time to time, This Is Glamorous may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Site. Those companies may use non-personal information about your visit to display ads for products or services which may be of interest to you.

## Affiliate Links

This Is Glamorous uses selective affiliate links, which means that a small commission is earned if you make a purchase via these links. The price you pay will be the same whether you use these affiliate link or go directly to the vendor’s website using non-affiliate links.

## Tracking & Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data stored in a user’s web browser while the user is browsing a particular website. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the website of the user’s previous activity. Cookies collect certain types of non-personal information such as search terms and specific web pages visited, the duration of these visits, and your preferences. This Is Glamorous does not use cookies, but our affiliates may, and these are governed by their own privacy policies.

## Links to Other Sites

In order to bring you the beautiful mix of design & décor, fashion, food, arts & culture, how-to’s and travel, This Is Glamorous often links out to other sites. We are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

## Modifications

This Is Glamorous may make changes to this privacy policy from time to time, so be sure to check back often if you are interested. We may amend or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review it periodically. Your continued use of the site after any change in this Privacy Policy will mean you accept such change.

## Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy, or about This Is Glamorous, please [contact us](http://www.thisisglamorous.com/contact/).

* * *
